Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art financial records, 1872-1988 COR0004.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Gallery and school budgets, 1934-1981; Series 4
  - Gallery: Excess Income/Deficit in Budget, 1952-1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Gallery: Fiscal vs. Calendar Year, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Gallery: Stocks-Market Value, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Art School Budget, 1969-1970; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Gallery Budget, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Gallery Budget: Department Budgets, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Gallery: Operation of the Budget-Quarterly, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Gallery Budget: Salaries, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Gallery Budget: Misc. Papers, 1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Art School Budget, 1970-1971; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Gallery: Budget, 1971-1972; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Gallery: Statement of Revenues, Expenses, & Fund Balance, 1971-1972; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Art School Budget, 1971-1972; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Gallery Budget, 1972-1973; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Gallery: Statements of Revenue & Expenses, 1972-1973; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1972 May-Dec; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Art School Budget, 1972-1973; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1973-1974; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Gallery & School: Statements of Income & Expense, 1973-1974; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Gallery: Proposed Budget, 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Gallery: Five Year Summary Statement, 1970-1974/1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Gallery: Restricted Funds Statements-Monthly-1-6, 1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Gallery Report-Mid-Year, 1975 February 28; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Gallery: Financial Report, 1975 June; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Gallery: Estimated End-of-the-Year Statement-Workpapers, 1974-75; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Gallery: Estimated End-of-the-Year Statement-Workpapers, 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Gallery Budget: Misc., 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Art School Budget, 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Gallery & School: Statements of Income & Expense-Monthly, 1974-1975; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Gallery: Budget-Proposed, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Gallery Budget, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Gallery Budget, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Gallery: Departmental & Events Budgets, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Gallery: Salary Proposals, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Art School Budget, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Gallery & School: Statements of Income & Expenses-Monthly, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Gallery: Budget, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Gallery Budget, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Gallery: Accounts Payable & Receivable Sheets, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements 9-10, 1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements 11-12, 1976; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements 1-2, 1977; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements 3-5, 1977; Series 4 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements 6-8, 1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Gallery: Condition of the Funds, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gallery: Departmental Budgets, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gallery Budget, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Art School: Budget, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Gallery and School: Statements of Income and Expenses - Monthly, 1976-1977; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Gallery Budget, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Gallery: Accounts Payable & Receivable Sheets, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1977 November-1978 March; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1978 April-August; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Gallery Budget, Miscellaneous, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Art School Budget, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Gallery and School: Statements of Income and Expenses - Monthly, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Gallery: Proposed Budget, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Gallery Budget, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folders 15-16)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Gallery: Cash Receipts, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Gallery: Compensation and Benefits Expenses, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Gallery: Departmental End-of-the-Year Estimates, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Gallery: Journal Entries, Budget Adjustments, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Gallery: Restricted Funds, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Gallery Budget: Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Art School: Budget 1978 April 17 Version, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Art School: Budget 1978 May 11 Version, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Art School: Budget Undated Version, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Art School: Budget Attachments, Charts, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Art School: Budget Deficit, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Art School: Budget Revisions, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Art School: Estimated End-of-the-Year Budget, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Art School: Line Item Analysis to Budget, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Art School: School Payment to Gallery, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Art School: School Salaries, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Art School Budget Miscellaneous, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Gallery and School: Statements of Income and Expenses - Monthly, 1978 September - 1979 February; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Gallery and Art School: Statements the Income and Expense Monthly, 1979 March - August; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Gallery: Budget 1979 July 11 version, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Gallery: Budget 1979 July 12 version, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Gallery: Budget 1979 July 12 version, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Gallery: Budget 1979 July 19 version, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Gallery and School Budget 1979 July 20 Version, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Gallery: Budget adjustments (Mid - Year), 1980 March; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Gallery: Cash Balances - The Funds, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Gallery: Cash Flow Statements, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Gallery: Departmental Budgets, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Gallery: Itemization by Topic, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Gallery: Restricted Funds Statements-Monthly, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Gallery Budget, Miscellaneous, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Art School Budget, 1979-1980; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Gallery and School: Statements of Income and Expenses - Monthly, 1979 September-1980 February; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Gallery and School: Statements of Income and Expenses - Monthly, 1980 March-1980 August; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Gallery and School: Budget, Miscellaneous, 1980-1981; Series 4 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Auditor's reports, 1939-1979; Series 5
  The reports are arranged chronologically.
  Contains semi-annual and annual reports from the auditing firms F.W. Lafrentz & Co. (1939-63), Raymond H. McGivern (1966-76/77), and Cooper & Lybrand (1977/78-78/79).
  - Auditor's Report, 1939; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 53-54)
  - Auditor's Report, 1940; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 55-56)
  - Auditor's Report, 1941; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 57-58)
  - Auditor's Report, 1942; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 59-60)
  - Auditor's Report, 1943; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 61-62)
  - Auditor's Report, 1944; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 63-64)
  - Auditor's Report, 1945; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 65-66)
  - Auditor's Report, 1946; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 67-68)
  - Auditor's Report, 1947 January-May; Series 5 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Auditor's Report, 1948; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 70-71)
  - Auditor's Report, 1949; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 72-73)
  - Auditor's Report, 1950; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 74-75)
  - Auditor's Report, 1951; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 76-77)
  - Auditor's Report, 1952; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 78-79)
  - Auditor's Report, 1953; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 80-81)
  - Auditor's Report, 1954; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 82-83)
  - Auditor's Report, 1955; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 84-85)
  - Auditor's Report, 1956; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 86-87)
  - Auditor's Report, 1957; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 88-89)
  - Auditor's Report, 1958; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 90-91)
  - Auditor's Report, 1959; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 92-93)
  - Auditor's Report, 1960; Series 5 (Box 8, Folders 94-95)
  - Auditor's Report, 1961; Series 5 (Box 9, Folders 1-2)
  - Auditor's Report, 1962; Series 5 (Box 9, Folders 3-4)
  - Auditor's Report, 1963; Series 5 (Box 9, Folders 5-6)
  - Auditor's Report, 1966; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Auditor's Report, 1967; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Auditor's Report, 1968; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Auditor's Report, 1971; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Auditor's Report, 1973-1974; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Auditor's Report, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Auditor's Report, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Analysis of Report, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Analysis of Report Data, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Auditor's Report, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Auditor's Report to Management, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Drafts of Audit, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Auditor's Report, 1978-1979; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Auditor's Report to Management, 1978-1979; Series 5 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Investment and Real Estate records, 1869-1979; Series 6
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged into 3 subseries: Riggs Bank, The Funds, and Real Estate Notes
  Related Materials
  Check the financial ledgers in Series 1 for related information.
  - Riggs Bank, 1952-1979; Series 6 Subseries 1
    Contains correspondence, memoranda, and quarterly, semi-annual, and annual stock statements concerning the bank's Investment Supervision Safekeeping Accounts (for Endowment Funds) with the Corcoran.
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1952 July-December; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 21-24)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1953; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 25-27)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1954; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 28-30)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1955; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 31-33)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1956; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 34-35)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1957; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 36-37)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1958; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 38-39)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1959; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 40-41)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1960; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 42-45)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1961; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 46-48)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1962; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 49-51)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1963; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 52-54)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1964; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 55-57)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1965; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 58-60)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1966; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 61-63)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1967; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folders 64-66)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1968; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folders 1-2)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1969; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1970; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1971; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1972; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Riggs Bank: Investment Supervision Accounts, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Funds, 1952-1979; Series 6 Subseries 2
    Materials are arranged by Fund and, thereafter, chronologically.
    Contains photocopies of a variety of information concerning the Endowment Funds, some from the Gallery's annual reports, until the consolidation of the funds in 1967/68.
    - Endowment Fund, 1888-1903; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Endowment Fund, 1904-1915; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Endowment Fund, 1915-1920; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Endowment Fund, 1921-1927; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Endowment Fund, 1928-1940; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Endowment Fund, 1941-1960; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Endowment Fund, 1960-1967; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Endowment Fund, 1971; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Endowment Fund, 1973; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Endowment Fund, 1974; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Endowment Fund, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Endowment Fund, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Endowment Fund, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Consolidated Endowment Fund, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Ann E. Clark Fund, 1927-1969; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folders 20-22)
    - W.A. Clark Fund, 1921-1969; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folders 23-26)
    - C.C. Glover, 1936-1949; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Mary Maxwell Fund, 1928-1969; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folders 28-30)
    - Membership Endowment Fund, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - A.W. Mellon Education and Charity Fund, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - James Parmalee Fund, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Euqene Wasz Mem. Scholarship Fund, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - The Yts. Zlotnick Fund, 1960; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Restricted Funds account, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Real Estate Notes, 1869-1979; Series 6 Subseries 3
    Contains appraisal certificates, correspondence, lease agreements, memoranda, and various mortgage and rental receipts. The Gallery bought and leased various properties and also dealt extensively in real estate mortgage notes for investment purposes from the 1870s through the 1950s. Important properties include Square 171, the Corcoran's original site on 17th and Pennsylvania (now the Renwick Gallery) which was sold to the U.S. Government in 1894; the property surrounding the original Corcoran site, which was rented out to various businesses, sold to a D.C. realtor, returned to the Corcoran during the Depression, rented atain to a parking service company, and finally sold to the U.S. Government in 1941; and the Abby + Frederic Parkhurst property, known as the "Edgemoor" estate (Montgomery County, MD), which the Corcoran foreclosed on in 1940 and sold to the Longfellow School in 1941. The bulk of the series is made up of files on mortgage note investments in D.C., Maryland, and Virginia on private homes.
    The series is arranged chronologically and, thereafter, alphabetically within years. Real estate note files are organized by the date the Corcoran assumed the note. These files often contain materials dating after the Gallery's assumption date.
    - Square 167 (Property Surrounding Original Gallery Site) 17th Street Property, 1869-1976; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 36-37)
    - Square 446, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Square 167 (Property Surrounding Original Gallery Site) 17th Street Property, 1877; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Square 406, 1878; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Square 446, 1878; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Square 167 (Property Surrounding Original Gallery Site) 17th Street Property, 1879; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Square 490, 1880; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Square 446, 1881; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Square 167 (Property Surrounding Original Gallery Site) 17th Street Property Sold to U.S. Government, 1894; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - 17th St. Property - Rental Agreements, 1911; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - 17th Street Property (sq. 167) - Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1911; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1912; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - 17th Street Property (sq. 167) - Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1912; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1913-1915; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 50-52)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1915; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1916; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1916; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 55-56)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1917; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1917; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1918; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1918; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1919; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1919; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1920; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1920; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 64-65)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1921; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1921; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - 17th Street Property - Rental Agreements, 1922; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - 17th Street Property- Rental Correspondence (Hagner), 1922; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 69-70)
    - 17th Street Property- Sale to Randall Hagner (CGA Holds Mortgage), 1923; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - 17th Street Property- Insurance Coverage, 1923; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - 17th Street Property- Randall Hagner, 1924; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - 17th Street Property- Randall Hagner, 1928; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - J.H. Wurdeman (Square 113, Lots 27-28), 1928; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - 17th Street Property- Randall Hagner, 1929; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - 17th Street Property- Randall Hagner, 1931; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Sanderson, Charles and Mabel: "Kalorama Heights", 1931; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - 17th Street Property- Randall Hagner, 1932; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Colt, Susan G.: Square 164, Lot 17, 1933; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Hagner, Randall: 17 St. Property - Return to CGA Ownership, 1933; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folders 81-82)
    - Moore's Gallery - Rental of 725 17th St., 1933; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1933; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Colt, Susan G.: Square 164 - Mortgage, 1934; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Moore's Gallery - Rental of 725 17th St., 1934; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Rental of 17th Street Property (Previously Owned by Randall Hagner), 1934; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - Wurdeman, J.H.: Square 113 - Mortgage, 1934; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Wurdeman, J.H.: Square 113, 1934; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Colt, Susan G.: Mortgage, 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Harry, Kachig: 1233-35 N.Y. Ave.-Mortgage, 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Johnston, James M. Jr. "Clean Drinking " or "Hayes" Property, 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property Rental (Previously Owned by Randall Hagner), 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Wurdeman, J.H.: Square 113-Mortgage, 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1935; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Colt, Susan G.: Square 164-Mortgage, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Ewell, Rose L.: 4529 Hawthorne St.-Mortgage, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - McKnew, Donald H.: 16 Kalorama Circle-Mortgage, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Miller, W.C.: 4517 Hawthorne St.-Mortgage, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property-Rental, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1936; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - MacFarland, Arabella A.: 2316 20th St. N.W.-Mortgage, 1937; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property (Square 167) Rental, 1937; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Mortgage Loans A-Z, 1937; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Misc. Real Estate Records, 1937; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Corte, Fallsta: 1600-1604 32nd St. (Mortgage), 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Horn, Betsy B.: 1525 14th St. (Mortgage), 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - MacFarland, Arabella A.: 2316 20th St. (Mortgage), 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Parkhurst, Frederic & Abby: "Edgemoor" Estate (MD.) (Mortgage), 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Service Parking Corp.: 17th St. Property (Rental), 1938; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 11, Folder 22)